{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8046971", "question": "What is throat cancer?", "topic": "31_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3581481", "question": "Is throat cancer treatable?", "topic": "31_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_dedad08c40164cee79464fdeb8da5e3e46b402ea", "question": "Tell me about lung cancer.", "topic": "31_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6661771", "question": "What are lung cancer's symptoms?", "topic": "31_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2509296", "question": "Can lung cancer spread to the throat?", "topic": "31_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2231504", "question": "What causes throat cancer?", "topic": "31_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7017761", "question": "What is the first sign of throat cancer?", "topic": "31_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_5295408", "question": "Is throat cancer the same as esophageal cancer?", "topic": "31_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7559909", "question": "What's the difference in throat cancer and esophageal cancer's symptoms?", "topic": "31_9"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_9f511bd0cba8a643a69264ccc42d4d3f50ec2d21", "question": "What are the different types of sharks?", "topic": "32_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6703005", "question": "What do Mako sharks eat?", "topic": "32_10"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7523018", "question": "How do Mako sharks compare with Tiger sharks for being dangerous?", "topic": "32_11"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_8159d5a26f607cc5069b6ac31c123b5113f1921c", "question": "Are sharks endangered? If so, which species?", "topic": "32_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2861210", "question": "Tell me about tiger sharks.", "topic": "32_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1102873", "question": "What is the largest shark ever to have lived on Earth?", "topic": "32_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_494547", "question": "What's the biggest shark ever caught?", "topic": "32_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2174108", "question": "What about for great whites?", "topic": "32_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_2e3aee7e462737cf2212a1518690df2739ec33a7", "question": "Tell me about Mako sharks.", "topic": "32_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2820324", "question": "What are Mako shark adaptations?", "topic": "32_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a91b0960b051a4372d86dd6efe245aa80940fe8b", "question": "Where do Mako sharks live?", "topic": "32_9"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_5954177", "question": "Tell me about the Neverending Story film.", "topic": "33_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3843635", "question": "What is the Neverending Story film about?", "topic": "33_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_161e2edabf7e5d5394c93756067f1a38a6ce29c3", "question": "How was the Neverending Story film received?", "topic": "33_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_3bce4220839bd4688f66f2c393abe864a8876171", "question": "Did the Neverending Story film win any awards?", "topic": "33_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_309a01bab60a38f6319b8705dabc3965f4f7ec10", "question": "Was the Neverending Story film a book first?", "topic": "33_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7273403", "question": "Who was the author and when was the Neverending Story book published?", "topic": "33_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4a3dd3779745688d8c51d6797910f019643bbdba", "question": "What are the main themes of the Neverending Story film?", "topic": "33_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_b9348816e6e63881858b3f42704e04204e4e5611", "question": "Who are the main characters of the the Neverending Story film?", "topic": "33_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_8fca165b9f59a4352f14f39e05389f6cbf62998f", "question": "Tell me about the Bronze Age collapse.", "topic": "34_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_50a0128560e0befcbd25a9a6b2b14fa94dd18abc", "question": "What is the evidence for the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_cded43587fd0308695dad1d0d9a1c1d4a57528bf", "question": "What are some of the possible causes of the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_15455b6dae847f52e816218c50dc823ca937585d", "question": "Who were the Sea Peoples during the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_15455b6dae847f52e816218c50dc823ca937585d", "question": "What was the role of the Sea Peoples in the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_cded43587fd0308695dad1d0d9a1c1d4a57528bf", "question": "What other factors led to a breakdown of trade during the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_1fd70e88d06da70de317cc423d3fd2770b55b5f3", "question": "What about environmental factors during the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_96f04b89c6b57bf3f3b236914e71b9299038b428", "question": "What empires survived the Bronze Age collapse?", "topic": "34_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_98a95d4704dfef815de8b4136585a6baf67aabec", "question": "What was the Stanford Experiment?", "topic": "37_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_ce14b58d20412dbac87893fc5241afc1e4f62e24", "question": "What did the Stanford Experiment show?", "topic": "37_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4cbd48dc8328602df3b555f4d399db5f98fceaaa", "question": "Tell me about the author of the Stanford Experiment.", "topic": "37_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_efb85354b19cf62de7a4bdffcd40d503cfb93a9b", "question": "Was the Stanford Experiment ethical?", "topic": "37_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_9fb2a1e33c6ccdf9fd5da36e198e338098336244", "question": "What are other similar experiments to the Stanford Experiment?", "topic": "37_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_fb009414929bfe036c16fcc2b8e43a7932716a1b", "question": "What happened in the Milgram experiment?", "topic": "37_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_0f97494cfe3ecd3e30904050f051c12daea2dac2", "question": "Why was the Milgram experiment important?", "topic": "37_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_e6e3c070144dc8649963f989fc267026d84bd86b", "question": "What were the similarities and differences between the Stanford Experiment and the Milgram experiment?", "topic": "37_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_7b57230c70924180246b25a77c9d74eda16ff49c", "question": "What are the origins of popular music?", "topic": "40_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_1cfdcdf9617a193d150920cdf551a02fcac6aa77", "question": "What are popular music's characteristics?", "topic": "40_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_0c28ac790b48bd0e2ddaa331495894099808a12a", "question": "What technological developments enabled popular music?", "topic": "40_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4c8df902420bc8ff5ea2aa01e75272438753e888", "question": "When and why did people start taking pop music seriously?", "topic": "40_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_0ccd84f8630dbf9d51d2ab15a0c2452943eed432", "question": "How has pop music been integrated into music education?", "topic": "40_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_631df0ce22c0a9353db337f2141b5bc14c428de0", "question": "Describe some of the influential pop bands.", "topic": "40_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_2c46cc70f460be0bde5abc276861ced4c90bc67b", "question": "What makes a song pop punk?", "topic": "40_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_497a528da6f88eb5e54a57947a306cc7fed1eeae", "question": "What is the difference between pop punk and emo?", "topic": "40_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_5099104", "question": "How was Netflix started?", "topic": "49_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2106478", "question": "How did Netflix originally work?", "topic": "49_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_5261498", "question": "What is Netflix's relationship with Blockbuster?", "topic": "49_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2480879", "question": "When did Netflix shift from DVDs to a streaming service?", "topic": "49_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8700077", "question": "What are Netflix's other competitors than Blockbuster?", "topic": "49_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8166235", "question": "How does Netflix compare to Amazon Prime Video?", "topic": "49_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_d207ca0054201c1930f117693fab68d79117748f", "question": "Describe Netflix's subscriber growth over time.", "topic": "49_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_26903b9b1ba84d65e9583a2ffcef10879a309f09", "question": "How has Netflix changed the way TV is watched?", "topic": "49_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_7864accd0e23c02ca7353aa521ad58cbd1ac93bf", "question": "What was the first artificial satellite?", "topic": "50_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1986854", "question": "What are the types of satellite orbits?", "topic": "50_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_cd4c39422e4d9cde0e891d8eedc5aea785952600", "question": "What are the important classes of artificial satellites?", "topic": "50_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_7e35955fa9dcce366df81284417c4f9e7b26791b", "question": "How do satellite navigation systems work?", "topic": "50_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a47cdd5dc6c04ef3eec33f2d9d8fa849deb89553", "question": "What is the Galileo system and why is it important?", "topic": "50_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_e7c874b162b319b646788097fefdb31d65abeb72", "question": "Why did the Galileo system create tension with the US?", "topic": "50_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_8a07418f0a35b41c81727cf31fbe386325e9b8fe", "question": "What are Cubesats?", "topic": "50_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_6a3c17f1c457e43d4413927b7e16dd40ad98287d", "question": "What are Cubesats' advantages?", "topic": "50_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4083277", "question": "What is worth seeing in Washington D.C.?", "topic": "54_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2874994", "question": "Which Smithsonian museums in Washington D.C. are the most popular?", "topic": "54_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_f31c92aada52df5b0f60a8e3b7f24d7c586bd8f5", "question": "Why is the National Air and Space Museum important?", "topic": "54_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8724939", "question": "Is the Spy Museum in Washington D.C. free?", "topic": "54_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8757859", "question": "What is there to do in Washington D.C. after the museums close?", "topic": "54_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6736378", "question": "What is the best time to visit the reflecting pools in Washington D.C.?", "topic": "54_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3726682", "question": "Are there any famous foods in Washington D.C.?", "topic": "54_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_62ab6e7d93e47c7d05380d9de7b695b605db0dc5", "question": "What is a DC half smoke?", "topic": "54_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_870574af91d72897cb3a08e05cfd6fd743d22e0d", "question": "Tell me about DC half smoke's history.", "topic": "54_9"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2530922", "question": "What is Darwin\u2019s theory in a nutshell?", "topic": "56_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2661358", "question": "How was Darwin\u2019s theory developed?", "topic": "56_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_0a02b3c081a75fa4456cc3ec266c2448653007eb", "question": "How do sexual and asexual reproduction affect Darwin\u2019s theory?", "topic": "56_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_9040cb8549b0fa6d244f65d1559e67fc2c5ba668", "question": "How can fossils be used to understand Darwin\u2019s theory?", "topic": "56_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_772b1bb2c666d70110466d0f04dd08e37b28c859", "question": "What is modern evidence for Darwin\u2019s theory?", "topic": "56_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_d0d0e8b736d06bcab535747b322cade02ad318db", "question": "What is the impact of Darwin\u2019s theory on modern biology?", "topic": "56_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_f038098df123c3567a0cf24690cf98e62e29e5cc", "question": "Compare and contrast microevolution and macroevolution.", "topic": "56_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_96e1ab73505e632a221817f28f98abf49779ece8", "question": "What is the relationship of Darwin's theory to speciation?", "topic": "56_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_66f66d43b5ccbfc7d6ba0ed7ac1d000457876c9b", "question": "What is a real-time database?", "topic": "58_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_66f66d43b5ccbfc7d6ba0ed7ac1d000457876c9b", "question": "How does a real-time database differ from traditional databases?", "topic": "58_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_66f66d43b5ccbfc7d6ba0ed7ac1d000457876c9b", "question": "What are the advantages of real-time processing in real-time databases?", "topic": "58_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_40979ef9c40980d39150cb1823bb967fa5532d4d", "question": "What are examples of important real-time databases?", "topic": "58_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4c996c157ef34e16b68bb0ea4af401a3579fbeda", "question": "What are important applications of real-time databases?", "topic": "58_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_113d8310658b8064d84d4c254f05ec9fc2e5a669", "question": "What are important cloud options for real-time databases?", "topic": "58_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_2dba24e34310221a0020ca9e58dc4064840f11fb", "question": "Tell me about the Firebase DB.", "topic": "58_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_2dba24e34310221a0020ca9e58dc4064840f11fb", "question": "How is Firebase DB used in mobile apps?", "topic": "58_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1200416", "question": "Which weekend sports have the most injuries?", "topic": "59_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6779241", "question": "What are the most common types of injuries?", "topic": "59_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3717892", "question": "What is the ACL?", "topic": "59_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a54c27a80bfa448127bead6a45133979ba0e0652", "question": "What is an injury for the ACL?", "topic": "59_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8757626", "question": "Tell me about the RICE method.", "topic": "59_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7787218", "question": "What is arnica used for in sports injuries?", "topic": "59_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_301840", "question": "What are some ways to avoid sports injuries?", "topic": "59_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2379978", "question": "Who are The Avengers?", "topic": "61_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2379978", "question": "Tell me about The Avengers' first appearance.", "topic": "61_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8193082", "question": "Who is the most powerful of The Avengers and why?", "topic": "61_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6325377", "question": "What is the relationship of Spider-Man to The Avengers?", "topic": "61_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8019905", "question": "Why is Batman not a member of The Avengers?", "topic": "61_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4b18b521b30a9d32d2c2852b05a5fffce336ca4e", "question": "What is an important team in the DC universe?", "topic": "61_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4e8eef22b8afd4025de4cd28d74a4efb0d598d98", "question": "Tell me about the origins of the Justice League in the DC universe.", "topic": "61_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_4b18b521b30a9d32d2c2852b05a5fffce336ca4e", "question": "Who are the important members of the Justice League?", "topic": "61_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_540109", "question": "Why is blood red?", "topic": "67_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_2531173", "question": "What foods contain high levels of iron?", "topic": "67_10"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_885881", "question": "What improves iron absorption?", "topic": "67_11"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1195872", "question": "What are red blood cells?", "topic": "67_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_bfcaf47f5b63cbed45d3686ffd733ee7ee3497bd", "question": "How are red blood cells created?", "topic": "67_3"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1436788", "question": "How is oxygen transported in blood?", "topic": "67_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_6200559", "question": "What is anemia?", "topic": "67_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_c736b3788b83aac23ccb620022e51964ebaad91d", "question": "What are the symptoms of anemia?", "topic": "67_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1360307", "question": "Can anemia go away?", "topic": "67_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_8b9d7f85d212920864fe31e201316027042e1e53", "question": "What are anemia's possible causes?", "topic": "67_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_716002", "question": "How is anemia treated?", "topic": "67_9"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a6764b19996a9360286a973000e4c3b70a0f0354", "question": "What is cuisine is Emilia-Romagna famous for?", "topic": "68_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_2a51e7bd37588de42e98a225c46bf9cd5dd021f9", "question": "What is the history of tagliatelle al ragu bolognese?", "topic": "68_10"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_ed61390b296c3beeeeabe3bb145dc62fde760eee", "question": "What are common variations of tagliatelle al ragu bolognese?", "topic": "68_11"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_1ea438efdfb51209784617f7dfbe7ab29085a8bc", "question": "Tell me about cooking schools and classes in Emilia-Romagna.", "topic": "68_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a6764b19996a9360286a973000e4c3b70a0f0354", "question": "What are famous foods from Emilia-Romagna?", "topic": "68_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_192c01b2083efc009e5d9b41cdc0ada4468480c9", "question": "Describe the traditional process for making balsamic vinegar.", "topic": "68_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_8599555", "question": "What is mortadella and where is it from?", "topic": "68_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4226769", "question": "What\u2019s the difference between mortadella and bologna?", "topic": "68_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4633852", "question": "Where was Parmesan cheese created?", "topic": "68_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1676685", "question": "What is done with the whey after production of Parmesan cheese?", "topic": "68_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a6764b19996a9360286a973000e4c3b70a0f0354", "question": "What are typical pasta dishes from Emilia-Romagna?", "topic": "68_9"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_5234962", "question": "How do you sleep after jet lag?", "topic": "69_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7981000", "question": "How about melatonin's effect for anxiety?", "topic": "69_10"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_bdc8d3a7ae55c0db5d5e12dd4d3201dcf0935cd4", "question": "Does melatonin help with jet lag?", "topic": "69_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_da17d8a585a2caf89eae83b9dc27926479f1cef6", "question": "How was melatonin discovered?", "topic": "69_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_44c4d90039478e22723a19c0c0a53efaee40496c", "question": "What are good sources of melatonin in food?", "topic": "69_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7976107", "question": "Is melatonin bad for you?", "topic": "69_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4836969", "question": "What are the side effects of melatonin?", "topic": "69_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_367324", "question": "Why does melatonin require a prescription in the UK?", "topic": "69_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_44c4d90039478e22723a19c0c0a53efaee40496c", "question": "How can I increase my melatonin levels naturally?", "topic": "69_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3960638", "question": "Is melatonin effective for treating insomnia?", "topic": "69_9"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_a43336b69a01972d6885ae62c3fd91becb15af69", "question": "Why do turkey and Turkey share the same name?", "topic": "75_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7775671", "question": "Where are turkeys from?", "topic": "75_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_cce033c1d52365f9582b5723238585d000a89cea", "question": "What was the importance of turkey in native cultures?", "topic": "75_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_decac487c810303730195f19ff73cf5bd98b91ed", "question": "When and how were turkeys domesticated?", "topic": "75_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_3ba52b0d8bb51efc5c12ef3a85e4e4467d69c3f7", "question": "Can turkeys fly?", "topic": "75_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_98c811d445645eecb8910e732fbe177f3a232af5", "question": "Why did Ben Franklin want turkey to be the national symbol?", "topic": "75_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_af1f4c832fdacb6e5cef273a1393411d8adffc56", "question": "Why is turkey eaten on Thanksgiving?", "topic": "75_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_ffbb032dd7f540ee2cb7e68d16e75945a0360381", "question": "What's the difference between soup and stew?", "topic": "77_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4452675", "question": "Is chilli a stew?", "topic": "77_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4948691", "question": "Is goulash a stew?", "topic": "77_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_873348cad14a217445aee3bbd35cdd75814a425d", "question": "What are popular stews in France?", "topic": "77_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_66eff27699239eb298881ab9f16759580ff73208", "question": "How is cassoulet made?", "topic": "77_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_1899968", "question": "Tell me about feijoada and its significance.", "topic": "77_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_22eea6a4446b399fc617ba7ad2a96c6b9bec39e5", "question": "How is feijoada similar or different from cassoulet?", "topic": "77_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_7440551", "question": "Tell me about Bigos stew.", "topic": "77_8"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_18cd058b20b933d141f07843595e74066f10875f", "question": "What is the keto diet?", "topic": "78_1"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3623247", "question": "Why was keto diet originally developed?", "topic": "78_2"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_3593755", "question": "What is ketosis?", "topic": "78_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_b5b05766afd890fcb7f889545534fb4f242d3e23", "question": "What is a paleo diet?", "topic": "78_4"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4813855", "question": "What do a paleo diet and a keto diet have in common?", "topic": "78_5"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4813852", "question": "How are a paleo diet and a keto diet different?", "topic": "78_6"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_435052", "question": "What is intermittent fasting?", "topic": "78_7"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4010757", "question": "How is intermittent fasting related to keto?", "topic": "78_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_394140", "question": "What is taught in sociology?", "topic": "79_1"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_651ebba2edda08211021651c58f9cc990d65258b", "question": "What is the main contribution of Auguste Comte to sociology?", "topic": "79_2"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_b534fa0fd8c22dea66bea198458582e8ab9799bc", "question": "What is the role of positivism in sociology?", "topic": "79_3"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_0488ef362023e7d7f83a7c3c7db62e3c820008a6", "question": "What is Herbert Spencer known for in sociology?", "topic": "79_4"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_b26113fc6e288cf01f88f3ee473d9592dd756132", "question": "How is Herbert Spencer's work related to Comte?", "topic": "79_5"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_b1a556af77d47462cb94769af9bbaf93a9eaf1ef", "question": "What is the functionalist theory in sociology?", "topic": "79_6"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_f304f1377652bef02572e36aa6e3f005fcc7c291", "question": "What is the main criticism of functionalist theory in sociology?", "topic": "79_7"}
{"bestanswer": "CAR_d6ecc524cd8e9622f8b8a5e4b54c7b3a7ddf2c77", "question": "How does functionalist theory compare to conflict theory?", "topic": "79_8"}
{"bestanswer": "MARCO_4711009", "question": "What are modern examples of conflict theory?", "topic": "79_9"}
